Inventory of the Misty Church collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Misty Church collection
1951-1981
83090
Church, Misty
6 manuscript boxes (2.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
The collection relates to Ronald Reagan, and especially to the presidential election of 1980 and the transition to the Reagan presidential administration. It is comprised of clippings, press releases, biographical data, speeches, photographs, and memorabilia.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1983.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection relates to Ronald Reagan, and especially to the presidential election of 1980 and the transition to the Reagan presidential administration. It is comprised of clippings, press releases, biographical data, speeches, photographs, and memorabilia.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Reagan, Ronald.; Presidents--United States--Election--1980.
Arrangement
Arranged as acquired
Collection Contents
- Africa, 1980 December 5 (Folder 1: 1)
  Clipping from New York Times article by Stephen J. Solarz
- Blacks, 1980 December (Folder 1: 2)
- Central/South America, 1979 February-1980 December (Folder 1: 3)
- Issue Network, 1980 March (Folder 1: 4)
- F10 Defense, 1980 November-1981 January (Folder 1: 5)
- Hostages in Iran (Folder 1)
  - Brzezinski comments, 1980 September 1-1980 October 17 (Folder 1: 6)
  - Brzezinski comments, 1980 October 26-1980 November 1 (Folder 1: 7)
  - Carter comments, before October 26, 1980 (Folder 1: 8)
  - Carter comments, 1980 October 26-27 (Folder 1: 9)
  - Miscellaneous Carter administration comments, before 1980 October 26 (Folder 1: 10)
  - Miscellaneous Carter administration comments, 1980 October 26-November 3 (Folder 1: 11)
  - Mondale comments, before 1980 October 26 (Folder 1: 12)
  - Mondale comments, 1980 October 26-November 1 (Folder 1: 13)
  - Muskie comments, before 1980 October 26 (Folder 1: 14)
  - Muskie comments, 1980 October 26-November 2 (Folder 1: 15)
  - Powell, Jody comments, before 1980 October 26 (Folder 1: 16)
- Madison Group, 1980 December (Folder 1: 17)
- F11 Policy, December 1980-January 1981 (Folder 1: 18)
- F15 Natural Resources, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 1: 19)
- F16 Presser Labor Ties, 1980 December 16-23 (Folder 1: 20)
- Women, 1980 December 8 (Folder 1: 21)
  Includes U.S. News and World Report, "Battle of the Sexes," on women in the workplace
- Reagan family, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 1: 22)
  Includes magazine articles and newspaper clippings on Nancy Reagan and Reagan family
- U.S. House of Representatives (Folder 2)
  - Burton, John L., undated (Folder 2: 1)
  - Murphy, John M., 1979 (Folder 2: 2)
  - O'Neill, Thomas P., Jr., 1974-1978 (Folder 2: 3)
  - Schroeder, Pat, undated (Folder 2: 4)
  - Wright, Jim, 1980 (Folder 2: 5)
- Executives, economists, and media (Folder 2)
  - Bradshaw, Thornton F., undated (Folder 2: 6)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., undated (Folder 2: 7)
  - Burns, Arthur Frank, undated (Folder 2: 8)
  - Connally, John Bowden, undated (Folder 2: 9)
  - Dickinson, William, 1978-1980 (Folder 2: 10)
  - Fraser, Douglas Andrew, 1980 (Folder 2: 11)
  - Friedman, Milton, undated (Folder 2: 12)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, undated (Folder 2: 13)
  - Greenfield, Meg, undated (Folder 2: 14)
  - Greenspan, Alan, undated (Folder 2: 15)
  - Harris, Patricia Robert, undated (Folder 2: 16)
  - Kilpatrick, James J., Jr., undated (Folder 2: 17)
  - Kirkland, Joseph Lane, 1980 (Folder 2: 18)
  - Laird, Melvin R., 1971 (Folder 2: 19)
  - Lapham, Lewis Jay, undated (Folder 2: 20)
  - Leontief, Wassily, undated (Folder 2: 21)
  - Norton, Eleanor Holmes, undated (Folder 2: 22)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, undated (Folder 2: 23)
  - Rohatyn, Felix George, undated (Folder 2: 24)
  - Rowan, Carl Thomas, undated (Folder 2: 25)
  - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1976; undated (Folder 2: 26)
  - Samuelson, Paul Anthony, undated (Folder 2: 27)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier, Jr., undated (Folder 2: 28)
  - Schlesinger, James Rodney, undated (Folder 2: 29)
  - Silk, Leonard Solomon, undated (Folder 2: 30)
  - Simon, William Edward, undated (Folder 2: 31)
  - Will, George F., undated (Folder 2: 32)
- U.S. Senate Republicans (Folder 3)
  - Armstrong, Bill, undated (Folder 3: 1)
  - Baker, Howard H., Jr., undated (Folder 3: 2)
  - Bellmon, Henry, 1979 (Folder 3: 3)
  - Boschwitz, Rudy, undated (Folder 3: 4)
  - Chaffee, John H., undated (Folder 3: 5)
  - Cochran, Thad, undated (Folder 3: 6)
  - Cohen, William S., undated (Folder 3: 7)
  - Danforth, Jack, undated (Folder 3: 8)
  - Dole, Bob, undated (Folder 3: 9)
  - Domenico, Pete V., undated (Folder 3: 10)
  - Durenberger, Dave, undated (Folder 3: 11)
  - Garn, Jake, undated (Folder 3: 12)
  - Goldwater, Barry M., 1980 (Folder 3: 13)
  - Hatch, Orrin G., 1979 (Folder 3: 14)
  - Hatfield, Mark O., 1980 (Folder 3: 15)
  - Hayakawa, S. I., 1979-1980 (Folder 3: 16)
  - Heinz, John, undated (Folder 3: 17)
  - Humphrey, Gorgon J., 1980 (Folder 3: 18)
    Includes memorandum and photograph
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1980 (Folder 3: 19)
  - Jepsen, Roger W., undated (Folder 3: 20)
  - Laxalt, Paul, undated (Folder 3: 21)
  - Lugar, Richard G., undated (Folder 3: 22)
  - Mathias, Charles McC., Jr., undated (Folder 3: 23)
  - McClure, Jim, undated (Folder 3: 24)
  - Packwood, Bob, 1980 (Folder 3: 25)
  - Pressler, Larry, undated (Folder 3: 26)
  - Roth, Bill, undated (Folder 3: 27)
    Includes three photographs
  - Schweiker, Richard Schultz, 1979 (Folder 3: 28)
  - Stafford, Robert T., undated (Folder 3: 29)
  - Stevens, Ted, undated (Folder 3: 30)
  - Thurmond, Strom, undated (Folder 3: 31)
  - Tower, John Goodwin, undated (Folder 3: 32)
  - Wallop, Malcolm, undated (Folder 3: 33)
  - Warner, John William, undated (Folder 3: 34)
  - Weicker, Lowell, 1980; undated (Folder 3: 35)
    Position papers
  - Young, Milton R., 1980 (Folder 3: 36)
- U.S. Senate Democrats (Folder 3)
  - Baucus, Mark, undated (Folder 3: 37)
  - Bayh, Birch, undated (Folder 3: 38)
  - Bentsen, Lloyd, undated (Folder 3: 39)
  - Biden, Joseph R., undated (Folder 3: 40)
  - Boren, David L., undated (Folder 3: 41)
  - Bumpers, Dale, 1979 (Folder 3: 42)
  - Burdick, Quentin N., undated (Folder 3: 43)
  - Byrd, Harry F., Jr., 1980 (Folder 3: 44)
  - Cannon, Howard, undated (Folder 3: 45)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1979 (Folder 3: 46)
  - Culver, John C., undated (Folder 3: 47)
  - DeConcini, Dennis, 1980 (Folder 3: 48)
  - Durkin, John A., undated (Folder 3: 49)
  - Eagleton, Thomas F., undated (Folder 3: 50)
  - Exon, J. James, undated (Folder 3: 51)
  - Ford, Wendell H., undated (Folder 3: 52)
  - Gravel, Mike, 1979 (Folder 3: 53)
  - Hart, Gary, 1980 (Folder 3: 54)
  - Heflin, Howell, undated (Folder 3: 55)
  - Huddleston, Walter D., undated (Folder 3: 56)
    Includes photograph
  - Inouye, Daniel K., undated (Folder 3: 57)
  - Jackson, Henry M., undated (Folder 3: 58)
  - Johnston, J. Bennett, 1980 (Folder 3: 59)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1979 (Folder 3: 60)
  - Levin, Carl, undated (Folder 3: 61)
  - Long, Russell B., undated (Folder 3: 62)
  - Magnuson, Warren G., undated (Folder 3: 63)
    Includes photograph (headshot)
  - McGovern, George, undated (Folder 3: 64)
  - Metzenbaum, Howard M., undated (Folder 3: 65)
  - Morgan, Robert, undated (Folder 3: 66)
  - Muskie, Edmund S., 1980 (Folder 3: 67)
  - Nunn, Sam, 1980 (Folder 3: 68)
  - Pryor, David, undated (Folder 3: 69)
  - Randolph, Jennings, 1980 (Folder 3: 70)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1980 (Folder 3: 71)
  - Sarbanes, Paul S., undated (Folder 3: 77)
  - Sasser, Jim, undated (Folder 3: 73)
  - Stennis, John C., 1978; undated (Folder 3: 74)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1980 (Folder 3: 75)
  - Stone, Richard (Dick), 1980 (Folder 3: 76)
  - Tsongas, Paul E., 1980 (Folder 3: 77)
  - Williams, Harrison A., Jr., undated (Folder 3: 78)
  - Zorinsky, Edward, undated (Folder 3: 79)
- Cabinet, 1980 December (Folder 4: 1)
- Subcabinet, 1980 December (Folder 4: 2)
- Reagan Brain Trust, 1980 December (Folder 4: 3)
- Biographies (Folder 4:)
  - Allen, Richard V., 1980 (Folder 4: 4)
  - Anderson, Martin, 1980 (Folder 4: 5)
  - Baldridge, Malcolm, 1980-1981 (Folder 4: 6)
  - Baroody, William J., (AEI), 1980 December (Folder 4: 7)
  - Bell, Terrel, 1981 January (Folder 4: 8)
  - Block, John R., 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 9)
  - Brady, James, 1981 January (Folder 4: 10)
  - Bush, George H., 1980 November-December (Folder 4: 11)
  - Casey, William J., 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 12)
  - Deaver, Michael K., 1980 December (Folder 4: 13)
  - Dole, Elizabeth, 1980 (Folder 4: 14)
  - Donovan, Raymond J., 1980 (Folder 4: 15)
  - Edwards, James B., 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 16)
  - Friedersdorf, Max L., 1981 January (Folder 4: 17)
  - Haig, Alexander M., 1979-1981 (Folder 4: 18)
  - Haig confirmation, 1981 January (Folder 4: 19)
  - Keating-Edh, Barbara, 1980 (Folder 4: 20)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 21)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1980 November-1981 January (Folder 4: 22)
  - Laxalt, Paul, 1980 November-December (Folder 4: 23)
  - Lewis, Andrew Lindsay, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 24)
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1981 January (Folder 4: 25)
  - Nofziger, Lyn, 1980 December (Folder 4: 26)
  - Pierce, Samuel, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 27)
  - Presser, Jackie, 1980 December (Folder 4: 28)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1981 January (Folder 4: 29)
  - Regan, Donald Thomas, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 30)
  - Sanchez, Philip V., 1980 December (Folder 4: 31)
  - Schweiker, Richard Schultz, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 32)
  - Stockman, David, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 33)
  - Smith, William French, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 34)
  - Trent, Darrell M., 1980 December (Folder 4: 35)
  - Watt, James G., 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 36)
  - Weinberger, Caspar, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 4: 37)
- Mayors (Folder 4)
  - Bradley, Tom, 1977 (Folder 4: 38)
  - Byrne, Jane M., undated (Folder 4: 39)
  - Feinstein, Dianne, undated (Folder 4: 40)
  - Koch, Edward I., undated (Folder 4: 41)
- Outsiders, 1980 (Folder 5: 1)
- Authors (miscellaneous contributors), 1980 (Folder 5: 2)
- Campaign request log, 1980 (Folder 5: 3)
- Campaign records, subscriptions and receipts, 1980 (Folder 5: 4)
- Transitions and organizations, 1980-1981 (Folder 5: 5)
- Transition personnel forms, undated (Folder 5: 6)
- Transition subscriptions, newspapers and magazines, undated (Folder 5: 7)
- Research library volunteers, 1980 (Folder 5: 8)
- Resumes, library, 1967; 1977,; 1980 (Folder 5: 9)
- Correspondence, library, 1980 (Folder 5: 10)
- Miscellaneous, administrative, 1980 (Folder 5: 11)
- Thank you letter to outsiders and staff of campaign, undated (Folder 5: 12)
- Telephone directory, state assignments to inaugural ball sites, 1980-1981 (Folder 5: 13)
- Transition phone directories, 1980-1981 (Folder 5: 14)
- Senate Republica contacts, undated (Folder 5: 15)
- Transition news summaries, 1980 December-1981 January (Folder 6: 1)
- Secretary of Defense Brown, Face the Nation, 1980 December (Folder 6: 2)
- Brzezinksy, Meet the Press, 1980 December (Folder 6: 3)
- Republican National Committee (Chairman's Report), 1980 January (Folder 6: 4)
- Increment of 1990 August, from Misty Church (Folder 6: 5)
  Includes original tickets to the 1981 Presidential Inauguration Ceremonies and the Inaugural Ball, "Honored Guest" medal of the Republican National Convention, and photographs of Reagan and inauguration
- Kiwanis International Proceedings, 1951 July (Folder 6: 6)
- Haig Senate hearing, 1981 January (Folder 6: 7)
- Task forces, undated (Folder 6: 8)
- Reports and journals, 1980 January-1981 February (Folder 6: 9)
- Reports and journals, 1980 September-1981 January (Folder 6: 10)